Volodymyr Gavrysh

Data Scientist / Machine Learning Engineer / Product owner

Ukraine, Kyiv | +380505865822 | vladimir101175@gmail.com



Summary

1.5+ experience in Data Science. Python, Pytorch, main ML libraries, Kaggle competitions, statistical analysis, product testing and prototyping.

12+ years of experience of developing market oriented solution (Travel, IT) Experience in business&product creation. Completed projects in IT, travel, governance.

Data Science skills:

- Analysis/Manipulation/Aggregation/Exploration. A/B testing.
- Applying different models and prediction algorithms, creating pipeline feature +engineering, models building, evaluation and implementation.
- Working with different Data Source.
- Data visualization, creation analytical reports.

Quickly learn new technologies and adapt them in projects. Proven results in business and public areas. Well developed presentation and communication skills.

Work experience

VP, Product Manager, Data Analytic

2018/09 - 2019/10

Sky Group - Barcelona, Spain

Responsibilities:

- USA / Europe market analysis, Business Analysis, Product Analysis
- Project coordinating between 3 IT teams to develop customer oriented product
- Agile development plans, creating technical specifications (TOV)
- Maintaining development logs, testing logs. (Lean Product Development)
- Product prototyping and testing.
- Sale support via training, solving individual cases with complex clients / partners
- Generate and implement marketing strategy for sales.
- Potential partner contacting, participation in exhibitions (California, UK, Germany)

Business Development Manager

2012/01 - 2014/05

Internet Travel Booking - Ukraine, Kyiv

IT startup with aim to develop innovative product and services in travel industry. *Responsibilities:*

- Market Analysis, Product Analysis
- Development product concepts (MVP), prototypes for testing user behavior
- Project/Product management of 4 products
- Formation of technical specifications for the IT development teams
- Preparation of a prospectus of investments, attraction of investments (CEO role)
- Financial planning of model development with passing a seed round
- Legal support of contracts of service providers

Competencies

- Data Analysis, Statistical Analysis
- Statistics, Probability
- CART modeling
- Supervised / Unsupervised ML
- Business development
- Marketing
- Product development
- Management

Technical Summary

Libraries / Languages / Tech

- Python 3.6
- SQL, Spark
- Sklearn, scipy, matplotlib
- Xgboost
- Dask
- Lightgbm
- CatBoost
- Pytorch
- Django 2.1
- Git, Heroku, PowerBI, Google DS

Data Science

- Calculus, math analysis, CART
- Linear models, Tree based models
- Boosting algorithms
- Pipelines
- CNN, LNN
- Hyperparameters optimization
- Ensemble modeling
- Data normalization standardization

Portfolio / Projects

https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/bankmarketing-campaigns-analysismachine-learning-volodymyr-gavrish/

https://github.com/VolodymyrGavrysh/ My_RoadMap_Data_Science/tree/maste r/data_analysis

https://github.com/VolodymyrGavrysh/ DataCamp_projects

Natalie-Tours - Ukraine, Kyiv

Responsibilities:

- Market & Product Analysis, Competitor analysis
- building a company from 0 point to one
- strategy implementation for Ukraine market
- marketing the products and services
- operation control of the company and building net of distributors and suppliers (airlines, hotels)

Education

Data science 2019

WorldQuant University

Computer Science scientific computing with Python for Data science

Master of Business Administration (MBA)

2012 - 2014

MIM-Kyiv Business School (MBA)

Master of Business Administration (MBA)

Python engineer 2018

Hillel (IT School)

Computer Programming

Python as programming language

Career Development

- Certified Data Scientist by Data Camp
- Data Analyst with Python Track by Data Camp
- EY Academy of business effective communication



StartUp in travel

One of the project web page.

